A Guide to the Lewis F. Powell Jr. Papers, 1929-1998
Washington and Lee University, School of Law, Lewis F. Powell, Jr. Archives
- Supreme Court of the United States 1968-1994 (bulk 1972-1987)
  - Speeches, Writings, and Interviews 1972-1987 (Box 287-302)
    - Speech Files 1972-1987
      - Dedication of New Sanctuary, Second Baptist Church, November 23, 1980 (Box 295)
      - Award from National Conference of Christians and Jews, December 10, 1980 (Box 295)
        Memorandum.
      - Monrad Paulsen, December 1980 (Box 295)
        Preface to Virginia Law Review issue dedicated to Paulsen.
      - Dinner Honoring Whitney North Seymour, January 8, 1981 (Box 296)
      - Testimonial Dinner for Chief Justice I'Anson, April 11, 1981 (Box 296)
        Portsmouth, Virginia.
      - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation In Law Award, April 13, 1981 (Box 296)
        University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia.
      - Bernard G. Segal - Bar Leader April 9, 1981 (Box 296)
        University of Pennsylvania Law Review Annual Banquet, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      - Fifth Circuit Judicial Conference, May 4, 1981 (Box 296)
        Biloxi, Mississippi.
      - American College of Trial Lawyers, August 8, 1981 (Box 296)
        New Orleans, Louisiana.
      - American Bar Association Annual Meeting, August 1981 (Box 296)
        Includes panel on reduction of trial delay and expense, and retirement Party for Bert H. Early. New Orleans, Louisiana.
      - Southampton Historical Society, August 18, 1981 (Box 296)
        Franklin, Virginia.
      - Justice Potter Stewart, September 1981 (Box 296)
        Tribute in Harvard Law Review.
      - Fifth and Eleventh Circuit Ceremonies, October 1 & 2, 1981 (Box 296)
        New Orleans, Louisiana and Atlanta, Georgia.
      - University of Virginia School of Law, October 19-20, 1981 (Box 296)
        Spoke informally to law classes. Charlottesville, Virginia.
      - University of Utah School of Law, February 5, 1982 (Box 297)
      - Cases of Interest This Term, May 3, 1982 (Box 297)
        Eleventh Circuit Conference, Kissimmee, Florida.
      - Carolene Products Revisited, May 11, 1982 (Box 297)
        Harlan Fiske Stone Lecture, Columbia University.
      - Washington and Lee University Board of Trustees Meeting, May 22, 1982 (Box 297)
      - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference, July 1-3, 1982 (Box 297)
      - Clement F. Haynsworth, Jr. -- A Personal Tribute, June 1982 (Box 297)
        Published in Washington and Lee Law Review, Winter 1982.
      - Bernard J. Ward, June 28, 1982 (Box 297)
        Published in Texas Law Review August 1982.
      - American Bar Association Annual Meeting, August 6-9, 1982 (Box 297)
        Includes interview with California Bar Association (August 6) and speech to ABA Division of Judicial Administration (August 9).
      - Statement at the Unveiling of the Portrait of Carlisle H. Humelsine, November 13, 1982 (Box 297)
        Williamsburg, Virginia
      - Dinner in Honor of Harry F. Byrd, Jr., December 6, 1982 (Box 297)
      - Ethyl Corporation 20th Anniversary Dinner, December 15, 1982 (Box 297)
      - Leon Jaworski, January 1983 (Box 298)
        Published in Baylor Law Review, Fall 1982.
      - Introduction of Justice Harry Blackmun to the Richmond Bar Association, February 16, 1983 (Box 298)
      - Judge Hardy Cross Dillard, February 1983 (Box 298)
        Published in Virginia Law Review, June 1983.
      - Chief Justice Marshall, March 27, 1983 (Box 298)
        Eminent Living Virginians Tribute, West End Rotary Club, Richmond, Virginia.
      - Clement F. Haynesworth, Jr. Federal Courthouse Ceremony, May 3, 1983 (Box 298)
        Greenville, South Carolina.
      - The Chief Justice's Proposal, May 8-10, 1983 (Box 298)
        Eleventh Circuit Judicial Conference, Savannah, Georgia.
      - Presentation of Cardozo Memorial Award to Justice Powell, October 9, 1983 (Box 298)
        Tau Epsilon Rho, Dearborn, Michigan.
      - Introduction of Chief Justice William H. Rehnquist to the Richmond Bar Association, February 14, 1984 (Box 299)
      - Phi Delta Phi Distinguished Service Award, March 12, 1984 (Box 299)
        Presented to Justice Powell. Washington, D.C.
      - Federal Bar Association, April 10, 1984 (Box 299)
      - Capital Cases, May 6, 1984 (Box 299)
        Eleventh Circuit Judicial Conference, Mobile, Alabama.
      - Response to Canadian Ambassador's Toast, June 21, 1984 (Box 299)
        Canadian Embassy Dinner, Washington, D.C.
      - Jackson Lecture, August 10, 1984 (Box 299)
        National Judicial College, Reno, Nevada.
      - American Bar Association Annual Meeting, August 2-9, 1984 (Box 299)
        Includes presentation of Justice Sandra Day O'Connor to the American College of Trial Lawyers (August 4), and Speech to Young Lawyers Division of ABA (August 5). Chicago, Illinois.
      - Conference of State Supreme Court Justices, February 13, 1985 (Box 299)
      - One Hundredth Anniversary of the Richmond Bar Association, November 1, 1985 (Box 299)
      - Retirement of Carlisle H. Humelsine from Colonial Williamsburg, November 16, 1985 (Box 299)
      - Breakfast Honoring Morry I. Leibman, February 16, 1986 (Box 300)
      - Introduction of Justice Sandra Day O'Connor, March 12, 1986 (Box 300)
        Richmond Bar Association.
      - Swearing-In of James L. Buckley as U.S. Appellate Court Judge, March 19, 1986 (Box 300)
        United States District Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia.
      - Palm Beach County Bar Association, March 14, 1986 (Box 300)
        West Palm Beach, Florida.
      - Eleventh Circuit Judicial Conference, May 12, 1986 (Box 300)
      - John Marshall Harlan May 15, 1986 (Box 300)
        American Law Institute Dinner, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C.
      - Presentation of the American Legion Distinguished Service Medal to Justice Powell, July 12, 1986 (Box 300)
      - Hunton & Williams Lawyers Luncheon, July 28, 1986 (Box 300)
      - The Burger Court August 12, 1986 (Box 300)
        American Bar Association Annual Meeting, Litigation Section, New York, New York.
      - The Forum Club, September 15, 1986 (Box 300)
      - ABA Committee on Law and National Security, September 18, 1986 (Box 300)
        University Club, Washington, D.C.
      - George Mason University School of Law, October 29, 1986 (Box 300)
        Arlington, Virginia.
      - Presentation of Chief Justice Rehnquist, March 9, 1987 (Box 301)
        American College of Trial Lawyers, Boca Raton, Florida.
      - Television Program with Fred Friendly and Justice William Brennan, October 29, 1986 (Box 300)
      - Tribute to Eugene Gressman, April 10, 1987 (Box 301)
        University of North Carolina School of Law, Chapel Hill, North Carolina.
      - Dedication of Albert V. Bryan United States Courthouse, May 1, 1987 (Box 301)
        Alexandria, Virginia
      - Eleventh Circuit Judicial Conference, May 11, 1987 (Box 301)
        Birmingham, Alabama.
      - Bill Moyers Interview, May 1987 (Box 301)
        Interview is basis for the Justice Powell installment of PBS and Public Affairs Television series In Search of the Constitution, first broadcast on June 19, 1987.
      - Foreword and Index re Judge John Butzner, June 20, 1987 (Box 301)
        Used in publication of Judge Butzner's opinions.
      - Introduction of Justice Scalia, April 15, 1987 (Box 301)
        Bar Association of the City of Richmond.
    - Research Materials
      - General 1985-1987 (Box 302)
      - Subjects
        - Access to Courts, 1976 (Box 302)
        - Bureaucratization of Federal Courts, 1982 (Box 302)
        - Crime in D.C., 1981 (Box 302)
        - Due Process and the Rule of Law, 1991 (Box 302)
        - Duty to Render Public Service, 1975 (Box 302)
        - Exclusionary Rule, 1981 (Box 302)
        - Federalism Under Pressure From Habeas Corpus, 1972 (Box 302)
        - Gun Control and NRA, 1988-1989 (Box 302)
        - John Marshall, 1973-1975 (Box 302)
        - Law Schools, 1973-1975 (Box 302)
        - Legal Profession, 1965-1987 (Box 302)
        - Next Speech, 1940 & 1980 (Box 302)
        - Portraits and Biography, 1983-1985 (Box 302)
        - Professional Responsibility, 1978-1981 (Box 302)
        - Supreme Court
          - History of Dissenting Opinions, 1974-1975 (Box 302)
          - Secrecy, 1975 (Box 302)
          - Stories and Jokes, 1972-1982 & n.d. (Box 302)
  - Trips 1972-1986 (Box 303-304)
    Trip Files, 2 cu. ft., includes records of both professional and personal trips. Forms of documentation found here include correspondence preceding and following the events, and records concerning travel and accommodations.
    - Honorary Degree, University of South Carolina, Columbia, South Carolina, May 13-14, 1972 (Box 303)
    - Vacation, Del Ray Beach, Florida, Jan. 22 - February 3, 1973 (Box 303)
    - Australia, July 1973 (Box 303)
      Did not make this trip.
    - Richmond, Virginia, July 23, 1973 (Box 303)
    - Lisbon, Portugal, August 1973 (Box 303)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, Greenbrier, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia August 16-18, 1973 (Box 303)
    - Washington Redskins Football Game, 1973 (Box 303)
    - Gridiron Dinner, Washington, D.C., April 6, 1974 (Box 303)
    - Stanford Law School, May & October 1974 (Box 303)
    - Fourth Circuit Conference, The Greenbrier, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, June 28, 1974 (Box 303)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, July 17-19, 1974 (Box 303)
    - Fishing Trip, Islamorada, Florida, July 1, 1974 (Box 303)
    - ABA Meeting, Honolulu, Hawaii, August 12-14, 1974 (Box 303)
    - Washington Redskins Football Game, October 20, 1974 (Box 303)
    - Honorary Degree, Wake Forest University, Winston Salem, North Carolina, May 19, 1975 (Box 303)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, The Greenbrier, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, July 31-August 3, 1975 (Box 303)
    - Moot Court, Brigham Young University School of Law, Provo, Utah, September 4, 1975 (Box 303)
    - Washington Redskins Football Game, November 2, 1975 (Box 303)
    - Moot Court, Harvard Law School, November 20, 1975 (Box 303)
    - Hunting with John McElroy, Chestertown, Maryland, December 1975 (Box 303)
    - Groundbreaking, National Center for State Courts, Williamsburg, Virginia, May 8, 1976 (Box 303)
    - Virginia Bar Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, July 15-18, 1976 (Box 303)
    - ABA Meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, August 1976 (Box 303)
    - Bohemian Grove, Monte Rio, California, September 1976 (Box 303)
    - American College of Trial Lawyers, Coronado, California, March 13-16, 1977 (Box 303)
    - World Peace Through Law, Manilla, The Philippines, August 21-26, 1977 (Box 303)
    - Moot Court, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 1977 (Box 303)
    - Moot Court, University of Chicago, May 3, 1978 (Box 303)
    - Dedication of National Center for State Courts, Williamsburg, Virginia, March 18-19, 1978 (Box 303)
    - Fifth Circuit Judicial Conference, New Orleans, Louisiana, April 23-26, 1978 (Box 303)
    - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference, The Greenbrier, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, June 28-July 1, 1978 (Box 303)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, July 20-23, 1978 (Box 303)
    - Honorary Degree, The Virginians of Maryland, January 20, 1979 (Box 303)
    - Jupiter Island, Florida February 1-4, 1979 (Box 303)
    - Gridiron Dinner, March 24, 1979 (Box 303)
    - The Greenhouse, Arlington, Texas, April 22, 1979 (Box 303)
      Only Mrs. Powell made this trip.
    - Moot Court, University of Michigan Law School, Ann Arbor, Michigan, April 3, 1979 (Box 303)
    - Fifth Circuit Judicial Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, May 6-9, 1979 (Box 303)
    - Moot Court, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 12, 1979 (Box 303)
    - Phillip Morris Christmas Party, New York City, December 18, 1979 (Box 303)
    - Hobe Sound, Florida January 1980 (Box 303)
    - Moot Court, University of Southern California, February 1, 1980 (Box 303)
    - University of South Carolina Choir Concert, Washington, D.C., February 6, 1980 (Box 303)
    - Gridiron Club, Washington, D.C., March 15, 1980 (Box 303)
    - School Board Banquet, Richmond, Virginia, May 9, 1980 (Box 303)
    - Honorary Degree, New York Law School, June 1, 1980 (Box 303)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, July 17, 1980 (Box 303)
    - Cornell Law School, Ithica, New York, October 9, 1980 (Box 303)
    - George Mason University, October 27, 1980 (Box 303)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Board Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia, November 15-16, 1980 (Box 303)
    - Fair Hope Farm, Maryland, December 19, 1980 (Box 303)
    - Hobe Sound, Florida, January 28-February 2, 1981 (Box 304)
    - Moot Court, Columbia University, New York City, April 7, 1981 (Box 304)
    - Class Reunion, Washington and Lee University, Lexington, Virginia, May 9, 1981 (Box 304)
    - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, June 1981 (Box 304)
    - Virginia Cultural Laureate Award, Richmond, Virginia, October 1981 (Box 304)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Board Meeting, November 13, 1981 (Box 304)
    - Hunting, Chestertown, Maryland, December 20-21, 1981 (Box 304)
    - University of Utah College of Law Alumni Association, Salt Lake City, Utah, February 5-8, 1982 (Box 304)
    - Hobe Sound, Florida, February 11-15, 1982 (Box 304)
    - Party for Georgene Biggs, New York City, March 19, 1982 (Box 304)
    - Gridiron Dinner, March 27, 1982 (Box 304)
    - American College of Trial Lawyers, Boca Raton, Florida, April 2-5, 1982 (Box 304)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, July 22-25, 1982 (Box 304)
    - Washington and Lee University School of Law, Lexington, Virginia, October 18, 1982 (Box 304)
    - Hobe Sound, Florida, February 3-7, 1983 (Box 304)
    - American College of Trial Lawyers, Boca Raton, Florida, March 4, 1983 (Box 304)
    - Gridiron Dinner, Washington, D.C., March 26, 1983 (Box 304)
    - White House Correspondents Dinner, Washington, D.C., April 23, 1983 (Box 304)
    - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, June 23-25, 1983 (Box 304)
    - ABA Meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, July 28-August 4, 1983 (Box 304)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Board Meeting, November 11, 1983 (Box 304)
    - Hobe Sound, Florida, February 8-12, 1984 (Box 304)
    - American College of Trial Lawyers, Maui, Hawaii, March 4-7, 1984 (Box 304)
    - Gridiron Dinner, Washington, D.C., March 24, 1984 (Box 304)
    - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference, The Greenbrier, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, July 27, 1984 (Box 304)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, July 19-22, 1984 (Box 304)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Board Meeting, November 9, 1984 (Box 304)
    - Eleventh Circuit Judicial Conference, Miami, Florida, May 12-15, 1985 (Box 304)
    - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, June 26-29, 1985 (Box 304)
    - ABA Meeting, London, England, July 1985 (Box 304)
    - Honorary Degree, Virginia Commonwealth University, Richmond, Virginia, October 8, 1985 (Box 304)
    - ABA Litigation Section Meeting, Dallas, Texas, October 25, 1984 (Box 304)
    - U.S. Senate Youth Program, Washington, D.C., February 2-9, 1986 (Box 304)
    - Gridiron Dinner, Washington, D.C., March 22, 1986 (Box 304)
    - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference, The Greenbrier, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, June 22-28, 1986 (Box 304)
    - Josephine R. Powell, London, England, June 28-July 2, 1986 (Box 304)
    - Harvard University 350th Anniversary, September 1986 (Box 304)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation Board Meeting, November 12, 1986 (Box 304)
    - Richmond Bar Association, January 29, 1987 (Box 304)
    - Devitt Committee Advisory Board, Laguna Beach, California, January 31-February 3, 1987 (Box 304)
    - Hobe Sound, Florida, February 7-12, 1987 (Box 304)
    - Gridiron Dinner, Washington, D.C., March 28, 1987 (Box 304)
    - Unveiling of Powell Portrait, Washington and Lee University, Lexington, Virginia, May 7-8, 1987 (Box 304)
    - American Law Institute, Washington, D.C. May 21, 1987 (Box 304)
    - Wilmer Ophthalmological Institute Advisory Council, Baltimore, Maryland, June 3, 1987 (Box 304)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, Virginia Beach, Virginia, June 20, 1987 (Box 304)
      Dinner honoring Oliver W. Hill and S.W. Tucker.
  - Retirement 1987 (Box 305-306)
    The retirement series includes "Retirement Record Volumes" and alphabetically arranged correspondence about Powell's retirement from the Supreme Court.
    - Letter and Statements of Resignation, June 24-26, 1987 (Box 305)
      Statement from the bench, statement to the press, and letter to President Reagan.
    - Correspondence
      - Selected Correspondence, 1987-1988. (Box 305)
        Correspondents include Justices, clerks and President Reagan.
      - General, 1987-1988 (Box 305)
        Alphabetically arranged by correspondent's proper name.
    - Scapbook Materials
      - Retirement Record Volumes, 1987-1988 (Box 306)
        The record volumes contain copies, bound in two volumes, of selected letters sent to Powell on his retirement from the Court. Volume II also contains clippings concerning his retirement.
      - Retirement of Lewis F. Powell, Jr. As Associate Justice of the Supreme Court, June 26, 1987 (Box 306)
        Copies of documents related to the announcement of Powell's retirement.
      - Tributes to Justice Powell In Law Reviews and Magazines, 1987-1988 (Box 306)
      - Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 306)
  - Calendars 1971-1987
    - Desk, 1972-1987 June (Box 307)
    - Pocket, 1971-1986 (Box 308)
      In addition to daily appointments, the pocket calendars include frequently called phone numbers written inside of their front covers and addresses near their back covers.
- Retirement 1987-1998
  Retirement papers, 40.5 cu. ft includes all materials created and collected by Justice Powell after his retirement from the Supreme Court in June 1987. As a retired Associate Justice, Powell maintained chambers in the Supreme Court Building until January 1997. He also maintained chambers in Richmond. He sat as an extra judge, primarily on the 4th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in Richmond.
  - Correspondence
    Correspondence includes the subseries: General Correspondence, Correspondence with Supreme Court Justices, Christmas Cards, and Correspondence related to Invitations.
    - General 1987-1998 (Box 311-315)
      The General Correspondence forms the conclusion to the series of the same name found in the 2.1.1 Personal Papers and 10.2.1 United States Supreme Court subgroups. Correspondence with family members from this period is filed in the "Family Papers" series of the 2.2.1 Personal Papers. Correspondence through 1998 with Powell Supreme Court clerks is found in the 10.2.3 United States Supreme Court papers correspondence series.
    - Supreme Court Justices 1987-1998 (Box 316)
      The correspondence with Supreme Court Justices continues the exchanges begun in Powell's 10.2.2 Supreme Court papers correspondence series.
    - Birthday Greetings 1996-1997 (Box 316B)
    - Christmas Cards 1996-1997 (Box 316B)
    - Declined Speech Invitations, 1987-1998 (Box 317)
  - Subject Files
    Some of these files begin in as early as 1962. Powell apparently transferred certain files from earlier periods to his retirement files and continued filing in them.
    - Addresses (Box 318)
      Arranged alphabetically with miscellaneous addresses at end.
    - Alibi Club
      - Correspondence, 1986-1998 (Box 318)
      - Printed Materials, 1975-1997 (Box 318)
        Includes membership lists and dinner menus.
    - Alfalfa Club, 1971-1996 (Box 318)
      Following correspondence, there is a separate file on dinners.
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1989-1993 (Box 318)
    - American Bar Association
      - Correspondence, 1987-1996 (Box 318)
      - Agreement with Soviet Lawyers, 1986 (Box 318)
      - Committee On National Security, 1987-1993 (Box 318)
    - American College of Trial Lawyers
      - Correspondence, 1971-1996 (Box 318)
      - Banquet, August 4, 1984 (Box 319)
      - Telephone Lists, 1987-1995 (Box 319)
    - American Law Institute, 1984-1993 (Box 319)
    - Automobile, 1962-1992 (Box 319)
    - Automobile Accident, June 20, 1991 (Box 319)
    - Baylor Law Review Tributes, January 1988 (Box 319)
    - Biographical Materials, 1988-1996 (Box 319)
    - Biography
      This file deals with John C. Jeffries, Jr.'s authorized biography, Justice Lewis F. Powell, Jr..
      - Correspondence, 1987-1996 (Box 319)
      - Printed Materials re, 1989-1994 (Box 319)
    - Bookbinding, 1972-1995 (Box 319)
    - Bork (Robert) Nomination to the U.S. Supreme Court, 1987 (Box 319)
      Includes memo to file of October 14, 1987.
    - Brennan (Justice William J.) Tribute, February 1991 (Box 319)
    - Bust of Powell, 1994-1995 (Box 319)
      Sculpted by George M. Kelly.
    - Capital Punishment, 1990-1994 (Box 319)
    - (Lincoln) Caplan Article, 1986-1987 (Box 319)
      Re the role of the Solicitor General for The New Yorker magazine.
    - Carnegie Commission On Science, Technology and Government, 1988-1990 (Box 319)
    - Cincinnati, Society of the, 1982-1996 (Box 319)
    - club Memberships
      - General, 1971-1996 (Box 319)
      - Richmond German, 1972-1994 (Box 319)
      - Waltz Group, 1990-1993 (Box 319)
    - Commonwealth Club, 1987-1993 (Box 319)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1987-1994 (Box 319)
    - Disqualifications, 1987-1992 (Box 320)
    - Distinguished Service Education Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 320)
    - Eleventh Circuit, 1981-1995 (Box 320)
    - Ethics In Government Act, 1988-1995 (Box 320)
    - Files of Lewis F. Powell, Jr., 1981-1992 (Box 320)
      Correspondence and memoranda about the disposition of Powell's papers. An inventory of personal files formerly held at the law offices of Hunton & Williams is at the end of the file.
    - Freeman, George C., 1988 (Box 321)
      Topic discussed is Freeman's Justice Powell's Constitutional Opinions in the Spring 1988 Washington and Lee Law Review.
    - Gunther, Gerald, 1987-1993 (Box 321)
      Re preface to Gunther's biography of Learned Hand.
    - Harbor Square Apartment, 1972-1990 (Box 321)
    - Harvard Law Review Tributes, 1987-1988 (Box 321)
    - Hunton & Williams History
      - General Correspondence, 1986-1995 (Box 321)
      - Anne Freeman Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box 321)
      - Drafts of Powell's Preface, 1989 (Box 321)
      - Research Materials, c. 1952-199 (Box 321)
        Includes Powell memorandum re Hunton & Williams history; typescript of Gay's c. 1952 firm history; 1974 memo re Albemarle-Ethyl Deal in 1962; biographical materials re George D. Gibson and Henry Anderson; and clippings, 1979-1991.
      - Reviews, 1990 (Box 321)
    - Inauguration of President Clinton, 1992-1993 (Box 321)
    - Intelligence Officers, Association of Former, 1989 (Box 321)
    - John Marshall Foundation, 1987-1992 (Box 321)
    - Jepson School of Leadership, 1989-1990 (Box 321)
    - Lincoln's Inn, Honorary Bencher of
      - Correspondence, 1970-1993
      - Print and Near-Print Materials, 1965-1995
    - Long, Carrie Lee, 1979-1990 (Box 321)
      Social Security information for Powell maid.
    - Lyons v. U.S. Supreme Court, 1988 (Box 321)
    - Mount Vernon Ladies Association, 1991-1995 (Box 322)
    - Murrow, Edward R., 1989-1993 (Box 322)